lecool.com 2019-02-14

# Privacy Policy -- Le Cool Weekly News

**LE COOL GROUP BV  
Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from www.lecool.com (the “Site”). 

**PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

 **Device Information**  
When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.” 

We collect Device Information using the following technologies:    

\- “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.  

 \- “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.   

\- “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site. 

**Personal Information**  
We may ask you for some or all of the following types of information which may be identifiable to you when you register for our Services, access various content or features, or directly contact the site: (i) contact information, such as your email address and name; (ii) your age; and (iii) information for the purpose of authenticating yourself or your account if we have reason to believe, in our sole discretion, that you may be violating site policies or for any other reason we deem necessary (collectively "Personal Information"). You are responsible for ensuring the accuracy of all Personal Information you submit.

 **Order Information**  
Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers), email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information.”

**HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

**Email Communications**  
We may use your email to deliver Le Cool's daily newsletter, as well as for other promotional (e.g., new product offerings, special offers by us or other third parties) purposes. Email messages we send you may contain code that enables our database to track your usage of the emails we send you, such usage includes whether the email was opened and what links (if any) were clicked. If you send an email to us, or fill out our "Feedback" form, we will collect your email address and the full content of your email, including attached files, and other information you provide.

We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). 

Additionally, we use this Order Information to: Communicate with you; Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services. 

We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns). 

**SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above.  For example, we use Shopify to power our online store--you can read more about how Shopify uses your Personal Information here:  https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy.  

We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site--you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here:  https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/.  You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here:  https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout. 

Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights. 

**YOUR RIGHTS**  
You have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below. 

Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above.  

Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including the United States. 

**DATA RETENTION**  
When you subscribe to our newsletter or when you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information. 

**MINORS**  
The Site is not intended for individuals under the age of 18.

 **CHANGES**  
We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons. 

**CONTACT US**  
For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at privacy@lecool.com or by mail using the details provided below:  Silodam 187, Amsterdam, NH, 1013AS, Netherlands
